Roi Revivo FS (Full-Stack) developer

0502855522 | roi14102000@gmail.com | Linkdin| Git Hub |MeDotCom

Summary

Experienced Full-Stack Developer with a **front-end focus**. Proven ability to build web applications using technologies like **React.js**, **Node.js**, **Nest.js**, and various front-end frameworks/libraries. **Strong problem-solving** skills. **Adaptable learner** with a successful record of acquiring new skills.

Education

Cyber Pro Full Stack Boot Camp

Ramat Gan,

Israel

Learned the basics of web development, starting with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, therAug. 2023 – March 2024 progressed to React (front-end) and Node.js (back-end) projects.

Experience

Full-stack developer

March 2024 - Present

Beer Sheva

IDF & Lotem & BI data

- Gain practical experience in web development in react.js, Nest.js and accept tasks at Jira.
- jump into a live project fixing bugs, create new futures, and collaborate with a team throws GitLab.
- Without knowing nest.js at the start. I successfully adapted, including backend-oriented solutions.
- Gain satisfaction by creating new features that Impact IDF command and control when we are in a war.

Security guard Intel

April 2022 – March 2024

Qiryat Gat

Combat solider

Aug 2019 – April 2022

IDF Nahal Gaza, Lebanon, Hevron

- Operated under high-pressure battlefield conditions, demonstrating resilience and commitment.
- Coordinated with fellow soldiers to achieve mission success, honing troubleshooting, and team collaboration skills.
- Maintained determination and perseverance, never backing down regardless of the difficulty or danger of the mission.

Projects

<u>Trip Planner</u> is a full-stack web application that helps users find flights, hotels, and attractions at their travel destination.

- Technologies: node.js, express, JWT, and SQL with sequelize ORM, react.js, Axios.
- Developed a full-stack web application using node is serving a REST API with React as the frontend.
- Implemented JWT to manage the session and security.
- use external API that provides data by coordinates query about the destination Hotels or attraction.
- design SQL relation DB that has FK logic to call the data effectively

CV Creator: Developed a web application for creating CVs with live updates based on user input.

- Technologies: Node.js, Express, JWT, MongoDB, React, React-Router-Dom, React-Hook-Forms, PDF-Render, Tailwind CSS.
- Faced the challenge of rendering PDF with on change update smoothly and handling complex forms at the same screen.
- Overcame the challenge by leveraging React Hook Forms and implementing debounce value to improve performance.

Contribution To Open Source

Maakaf Open-Source, Israeli open-source community.

- Actively developed new features for a working website.
- Communicated with clients (head of Maakaf) to understand and implement their needs.
- Collaborated with different teams and gathered my own team and worked with GitHub.
- Dive into a next.js project without knowing the framework. I successfully adapted and acquired the skill.

Technical Skills

Languages: Python, JS (JavaScript), HTML / CSS Frameworks: Next.js, Node.js, Django, React Native

Developer Tools: Git, GitLab, VS Code, Visual Studio, MongoDB, SQL

Libraries: Selenium, SQL ORM (Sequelize), React.js, Redux.js

JWT, react-hook-forms, react-router-Dom, skeleton, PDF.render, Axius, tailwind CSS, SCSS